giveaway.ly 2014-05-01

# Privacy Policy : Giveaway.ly | Sponsored Giveaways

### Privacy Policy:

Giveaway.ly is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. 

This Privacy Policy provides an explanation as to what happens to any personal data that you provide to us, or that we collect from you. 

We reserve the right to make periodic changes to our privacy policy without notice. 

#### Information We Collect

  * Details of your visits to our website and the resources that you access, including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data.
  * 2\. Information that you provide by filling in forms on our website, such as when you signup to our newsletter, register for information. Though we don’t store any of your payment details at our end (It stays at the merchant processor (PayPal / 2CO/ Payment gateway) Information provided to us when you communicate with us for any reason.

#### Use of Cookies

We may gather information about your computer for our services and to provide statistical information regarding the use of our website to our advertisers. Such information will not identify you personally it is statistical data about our visitors and their use of our site. This statistical data does not identify any personal details whatsoever. 

#### Use of Your Information

The information that we collect and store relating to you is primarily used to enable us to provide our services to you. In addition, we may use the information for the following purposes: 

  * To provide you with information requested from us, relating to our products or services. To provide information on other products which we feel may be of interest to you, where you have consented to receive such information.
  * To meet our contractual commitments to you.
  * To notify you about any changes to our website, such as improvements or service/product changes, that may affect our service.

All email addresses and other contact information is used internally only and is NEVER sold, rented, or otherwise passed on to anybody outside of our company. We value your privacy. Please be advised that we do not reveal information about identifiable individuals to our advertisers but we may, on occasion, provide them with aggregate statistical information about our visitors. 

#### Third Party Links

You might find links to third party websites on our website. These websites should have their own privacy policies which you should check. We do not accept any responsibility or liability for their policies whatsoever as we have no control over them. 

#### Consent

By using this site, you consent to the collection and use of information as outlined in the above documentation. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. 

#### Questions or Comments:

If you have any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us by e-mail at [cs@giveaway.ly](mailto:cs@giveaway.ly)  
or by mail to  
2510 Warren Ave  
Cheyenne,  
WY 82001-3163.
